IBT0062
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 848 - Harold Gimby's Files
1957-1996
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Gimbey, Harold
IBT0062
1 Linear Feet 1 record center carton
This collection contains correspondence, news clippings, newsletters, labor pamphlets, local union grievance forms and receipts, and elections materials from Local Union 848. Materials are dated from 1957-1996. These are the records of Harold Gimby, a member of Local 848 based on Los Angeles, California.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, news clippings, newsletters, labor pamphlets, local union grievance forms and receipts, and elections materials from Local Union 848. Materials are dated from 1957-1996.
Arrangement
Materials are organized into 1 series: Local 848-Harold Gimby's Files
Biographical
Harold Ellsworth Gimby was secretary-treasurer of Teamsters Local 848 in the 1960s. He was born in 1911 and died in 2011.
Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This materials was transferred to the TLHRC from the IBT.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Gimbey, Harold
- Local 848 Harold Gimby Files, 1957-1996; Series 1
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Correspondences, 1966-1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Legislative Information, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files General, 1960-1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Newspapers and Newsletters, 1967-1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Forms, 1967, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Labor-Management Reporting & Disclosure Act, 1963-1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Receipts, 1964-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Resolution, 1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Agreements, 1968-1969; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Union Elections General, 1967, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Local 848 Elections, 1965-1972; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings General Labor, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Food Industry, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Legal Cases and Decisions, 1968-1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Reagan Election, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Teamsters General, 1957-1978; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Trucking Industry, 1970, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Pension Benefits, 1967-1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Clippings Worker Wages, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files IBT Labor Institute 1970, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Econ/Social Legislation Western Confernce of Teamsters, n.d.; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 848 Harold Gimby's Files Western Confernce of Teamsters Workshop, 1968; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)